export default data = [
  {
      question: "The movie director adapted this year’s bestseller into a hit and made a ______.",
      options: ["fortune","request","companion","decision"],
      correct_option: "fortune"
  },
  {
      question: "Wang Chien-ming, the Yankees’ best pitcher last year, already showed his great _____ for baseball when he was still a teenager.",
      options: ["response","reluctance","permission","potential"],
      correct_option: "potential"
  },
  {
      question: "Although Jeffery had to keep two part-time jobs to support his family, he never ______ his studies. In fact, he graduated with honors.",
      options: ["neglected","segmented","financed","diminished"],
      correct_option: "neglected"
  },
  {
      question: "If it is too cold in this room, you can ______ the air conditioner to make yourself feel comfortable.",
      options: ["fasten","adjust","defeat","upload"],
      correct_option: "adjust"
  },
  {
      question: "This course will provide students with a solid ______ for research. It is highly recommended for those who plan to go to graduate school.",
      options: ["admission","circulation","foundation","extension"],
      correct_option: "foundation"
  },
  {
      question: "Peter is now living on a ______ of NT$100 per day. He cannot afford any recreational activities.",
      options: ["division","guidance","measure","budget"],
      correct_option: "budget"
  },
  {
      question: "Amy succeeded in ______ for a raise though her boss didn’t agree to increase her salary at first.",
      options: ["compensating","negotiating","substituting","advertising"],
      correct_option: "negotiating"
  },
  {
      question: "Ms. Li’s business ______ very quickly. She opened her first store two years ago; now she has fifty stores all over the country.",
      options: ["discouraged","transferred","stretched","expanded"],
      correct_option: "expanded"
  },
  {
      question: "Ruth is a very ____ person. She cannot take any criticism and always finds excuses to justify herself.",
      options: ["shameful","innocent","defensive","outgoing"],
      correct_option: "defensive"
  },
  {
      question: "It’s a pity that you have to leave so soon. I ______ hope that you will come back very soon.",
      options: ["sincerely","scarcely","reliably","obviously"],
      correct_option: "sincerely"
  },
  {
      question: "We human beings may live without clothes, but food and air are ______ to our life.",
      options: ["magnificent","essential","influential","profitable"],
      correct_option: "essential"
  },
  {
      question: "The manager ______ without hesitation after he had been offered a better job in another company.",
      options: ["retreated","revived","removed","resigned"],
      correct_option: "resigned"
  },
  {
      question: "Many important legal ______ concerning the tragic incident have now been preserved in the museum.",
      options: ["distributions","formations","documents","constructions"],
      correct_option: "documents"
  },
  {
      question: "I’m not sure exactly how much scholarship you’ll receive, but it will _____ cover your major expenses.",
      options: ["recently","roughly","frankly","variously"],
      correct_option: "roughly"
  },
  {
      question: "Tom was very ill a week ago, but now he looks healthy. We are ______ by his quick recovery.",
      options: ["amazed","convinced","advised","confirmed"],
      correct_option: "amazed"
  },
]
